CHI-JUI WU

Website http://chijuiwu.space
Email chijui@chijuiwu.space
GitHub @cjw-charleswu

RESEARCH STATEMENT

My research interests include sensing technologies, mobile devices, ubiquitous computing, proxemic interaction, and machine learning. I build novel interactive systems for groups and multi-device environments, and leverage machine intelligence to improve human-computer interaction. Recently, I have developed a new tracking infrastructure that enables HCI researchers to build and evaluate proxemic-aware, activity and device-centric interfaces. In my further research, I would like to design and create new cross-device interactions for individuals and groups in various environments. I am also interested in the research field of computer science education.

EDUCATION

MRes. Computational Statistics and Machine Learning, Distinction

2015 - 2016

University College London, United Kingdom Supervisors: Prof. Nicolai Marquardt, Prof. Steven Houben

BSc. Computer Science, First-Class Honours

University of St Andrews, United Kingdom Supervisor: Prof. David Harris-Birtill

2011 - 2015

PUBLICATIONS

[C.1] Wu, CJ., Houben, S., Marquardt, N. (2017) EagleSense: Tracking People and Devices in Interactive Spaces using Real-Time Top-View Depth-Sensing. To appear In *Proceedings of the 35th Annual ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems* (Denver, Colorado, USA, May 6 - 11, 2017). CHI '17. ACM, New York, NY, USA.

[J.1] Wu, CJ., Quigley, A., Harris-Birtill, D. (2016) Out of Sight: A Toolkit for Tracking Occluded Human Joint Positions. In *Personal and Ubiquitous Computing*, 21(1), 125-135.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Research Intern, University of St Andrews, United Kingdom; Jisc

June 2015 to

Explored novel system infrastructures with virtual machines and continuous integration tools for software recomputation (recomputation.org)

Supervisor: Prof. Ian Gent

September 2015

Research Intern, University of St Andrews, United Kingdom

June2014 to September 2014

Developed and evaluated user interfaces with depth-sensing visualization feedback for group collaboration.

Supervisors: Prof. Aaron Quigley, Prof. Per Ola Kristensson

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant, Wanrong Junior High School, Hualien, Taiwan

Teaching English (middle school) in remote rural areas in Taiwan for substitute military service.

January 2016 to January 2018

Tutor

TUTORING EXPERIENCE

Mathematics and Chemistry (High school), Computer Science (University), English (Elementary school)

2010 - Present

Game engines

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

Honorable mention, University College London Data Science Student Challenge (United Kingdom)	02/2016
Best use of Mendeley API, Hack Cambridge (United Kingdom)	01/2016
Finalist, Barclays Openminds Hackathon (United Kingdom)	11/2013
First, J.P. Morgan Code for Good Challenge (United Kingdom)	11/2013
Dean's List, University of St Andrews (United Kingdom)	06/2015
Dean's List, University of St Andrews (United Kingdom)	06/2014
Presidential Award, American International School of Guangzhou (China)	06/2011

SKILLS

Git, TravisCl, Bash, Batch, Unix Miscellaneous Java, Python, C, C++, C#, Matlab, JavaScript, Go Programming OpenCV, EmguCV languages Scikit-Learn, XGBoost, Keras Computer vision Numpy, Scipy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn Machine learning Markdown, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, WebGL, D3.js, Flask, Tornado, Django Scientific computing Microsoft Kinect, Phidget, Arduino Web technologies Swing, JavaFX, WinForms, WPF Sensors and Vagrant hardware Unreal Engine, Phaser, pixi.js **GUI** frameworks Virtual machines

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITIES

Treasurer, University of St Andrews Computing Society (United Kingdom)	05/2014 – 05/2015
Secretary, University of St Andrews Psychology Society (United Kingdom)	05/2013 - 05/2014
Events coordinator, University of St Andrews Psychology Society (United Kingdom)	05/2012 - 05/2013
First-year representative, University of St Andrews Breakaway (Hill-Walking) Society (United Kingdom)	09/2011 – 12/2011